[
  {
    "timestamp": "2026-01-18T02:33:01.242Z",
    "title": "Full Stack Engineer (MERN) — AI Fintech | In-Office (NYC)",
    "company": "FinTech AI & Blockchain Startup",
    "link": "https://www.linkedin.com/jobs/collections/recommended/post-apply/default/?currentJobId=4321578276&discover=recommended&discoveryOrigin=JOBS_HOME_JYMBII&postApplyJobId=4321578276",
    "profileId": "custom_1768703460835",
    "log": [
      {
        "question": "Mobile phone number",
        "answer": "3035321111",
        "type": "pre-fill"
      },
      {
        "question": "Email address Email address",
        "answer": "mark.candaras+linkedin@gmail.com",
        "type": "pre-fill"
      },
      {
        "question": "Phone country code Phone country code",
        "answer": "United States (+1)",
        "type": "pre-fill"
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the last two numerical digits of Edison's lightbulb patent?",
        "answer": "No",
        "type": "ai"
      },
      {
        "question": "Do you live in the NYC metro, and are you comfortable working from our NYC office Monday through Thursday? Do you live in the NYC metro, and are you comfortable working from our NYC office Monday through Thursday?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "type": "ai"
      },
      {
        "question": "Are you currently using AI tools such as Cursor? Are you currently using AI tools such as Cursor?",
        "answer": "\"Yes\"",
        "type": "ai"
      },
      {
        "question": "Are you willing to undergo a background check, in accordance with local law/regulations? Are you willing to undergo a background check, in accordance with local law/regulations?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "type": "pre-fill"
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the last two numerical digits of Edison's lightbulb patent?",
        "answer": "No",
        "type": "pre-fill"
      },
      {
        "question": "Do you live in the NYC metro, and are you comfortable working from our NYC office Monday through Thursday? Do you live in the NYC metro, and are you comfortable working from our NYC office Monday through Thursday?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "type": "pre-fill"
      },
      {
        "question": "Are you currently using AI tools such as Cursor? Are you currently using AI tools such as Cursor?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "type": "pre-fill"
      },
      {
        "question": "Are you willing to undergo a background check, in accordance with local law/regulations? Are you willing to undergo a background check, in accordance with local law/regulations?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "type": "pre-fill"
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the last two numerical digits of Edison's lightbulb patent?",
        "answer": "No",
        "type": "pre-fill"
      },
      {
        "question": "Do you live in the NYC metro, and are you comfortable working from our NYC office Monday through Thursday? Do you live in the NYC metro, and are you comfortable working from our NYC office Monday through Thursday?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "type": "pre-fill"
      },
      {
        "question": "Are you currently using AI tools such as Cursor? Are you currently using AI tools such as Cursor?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "type": "pre-fill"
      },
      {
        "question": "Are you willing to undergo a background check, in accordance with local law/regulations? Are you willing to undergo a background check, in accordance with local law/regulations?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "type": "pre-fill"
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the last two numerical digits of Edison's lightbulb patent?",
        "answer": "98",
        "type": "pre-fill"
      },
      {
        "question": "Do you live in the NYC metro, and are you comfortable working from our NYC office Monday through Thursday? Do you live in the NYC metro, and are you comfortable working from our NYC office Monday through Thursday?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "type": "pre-fill"
      },
      {
        "question": "Are you currently using AI tools such as Cursor? Are you currently using AI tools such as Cursor?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "type": "pre-fill"
      },
      {
        "question": "Are you willing to undergo a background check, in accordance with local law/regulations? Are you willing to undergo a background check, in accordance with local law/regulations?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "type": "pre-fill"
      },
      {
        "question": "Are you legally authorized to work in the United States? Are you legally authorized to work in the United States?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "type": "pre-fill"
      },
      {
        "question": "Will you now, or in the future, require sponsorship for employment visa status (e.g. H-1B visa status)? Will you now, or in the future, require sponsorship for employment visa status (e.g. H-1B visa status)?",
        "answer": "No",
        "type": "pre-fill"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2026-01-18T02:31:51.113Z",
    "title": "Senior Systems Engineer – Front Office Technology",
    "company": "Summit Tech Partners",
    "link": "https://www.linkedin.com/jobs/collections/recommended/post-apply/default/?currentJobId=4346183225&discover=recommended&discoveryOrigin=JOBS_HOME_JYMBII&postApplyJobId=4346183225",
    "profileId": "custom_1768703460835",
    "log": [
      {
        "question": "Mobile phone number",
        "answer": "3035321111",
        "type": "pre-fill"
      },
      {
        "question": "Email address Email address",
        "answer": "mark.candaras+linkedin@gmail.com",
        "type": "pre-fill"
      },
      {
        "question": "Phone country code Phone country code",
        "answer": "United States (+1)",
        "type": "pre-fill"
      },
      {
        "question": "How many years of work experience do you have with Amazon Web Services (AWS)?",
        "answer": "15",
        "type": "pre-fill"
      },
      {
        "question": "How many years of work experience do you have with Google Cloud Platform (GCP)?",
        "answer": "10",
        "type": "pre-fill"
      },
      {
        "question": "How many years of work experience do you have with .NET Framework?",
        "answer": "5",
        "type": "pre-fill"
      },
      {
        "question": "Are you willing to undergo a background check, in accordance with local law/regulations? Are you willing to undergo a background check, in accordance with local law/regulations?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "type": "pre-fill"
      },
      {
        "question": "Are you comfortable working in a hybrid setting? Are you comfortable working in a hybrid setting?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "type": "pre-fill"
      },
      {
        "question": "Are you comfortable commuting to this job's location? Are you comfortable commuting to this job's location?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "type": "ai"
      },
      {
        "question": "Are you legally authorized to work in the United States? Are you legally authorized to work in the United States?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "type": "pre-fill"
      }
    ]
  }
]